pakwired.com 2019-10-31

# PakWired - Latest Startup and Technology News from Pakistan - PakWired is all about business, technology and startup culture.

You consent to the use of your personal information by PakWired.com and/or its third party providers and distributors in accordance with the terms of and for the purposes set forth in our Privacy Policy. PakWired’s Business Showcase does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

PakWired.com provides the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with PakWired under extremely strict confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help PakWired communicate with you about offers from PakWired and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

You may choose to give us personal information, such as your name, contact number, address or e-mail id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you, to participate on the site, forum, contests, use of softwares, articles, white papers or to provide you with a subscription. If you tell us that you do not want us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. PakWired may share your information with its business partners who sponsor an event, white paper downloads, contest, or promotion; or who jointly offer a service or feature with PakWired.com.

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender email id with details of the correction requested.

We sometimes collect anonymous information from visits to our sites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we also measure visitor activity on PakWired web site, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. PakWired or its affiliates or vendors may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service. We maintain the highest levels of confidentiality for this information; our affiliates and vendors follow the same high levels of confidentiality. This anonymous information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner, you can either disable your cookies.

PakWired may, if you so choose, send direct mailers to you at the address given by you. You have the option to ‘opt-out’ of this direct mailer by way of links provided at the bottom of each mailer. We respect your privacy and in the event that you choose to not receive such mailers, we will take all steps to remove you from the list.

We transfer information about you if PakWired is acquired by or merged with another company.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

PakWired reserves the right to use the information to provide the user a more personalized online experience. PakWired provides links to web sites and access to content, products and services from third parties, including users, advertisers, affiliates and sponsors of the Site. You agree that PakWired is not responsible for the availability of, and content provided on, third party web sites. The User is requested to peruse the policies posted by other web sites regarding privacy and other topics before use. PakWired is not responsible for third party content accessible through the Site, including opinions, advice, statements and advertisements, and user shall bear all risks associated with the use of such content. PakWired is not responsible for any loss or damage of any sort user may incur from dealing with any third party.

We use the information we collect to:  
Provide you the services that you have requested. Tell you about exciting offers which we think you will value. Customize the content and advertising that you see on PakWired.com. Improve your experience on PakWired.com. As otherwise described to you at the point of collection or with your consent.

How to contact us: If you have a technical or general support question, please visit <https://pakwired.com/contact/> to reach out to us directly.
